电视:周六体育焦点继续是全国大专学院拉拉队长四分之一决赛.金黄色分区.
TV: The Saturday sports spectacular continues with the national junior collegiate cheerleaders quarter finals.Blonde
division
本:棒极了!
Ben: Alright!
电视:不要碰那个按纽.
TV: Don't touch that dial.
本:我什么都不碰.
Ben: I ain't touching nothing.
克莉丝:你在看什么,本?
Chrissy: What are you watching Ben?
本:克莉丝,你非要来这里面吃早饭吗?
Ben: Chrissy, do you have to eat your breakfast in here?
开萝尔:失,她必须.你看什么呢?
Carol: Yes she does.What are you watching?
本:肯定是卡通片.
Ben: Cartoons apparently.
迈克:嗨,爸爸!
Mike: Hey dad!
开萝尔:在楼上.
Carol: He's upstairs.
迈克:嗨,爸爸!
Mike: Hey Dad!
开萝尔:你要这么吼叫吗?
Carol: Must you yell?
迈克:如果他听不见怎么办?嗨,爸爸,如果你要带我去健身房,我准备好了.我还没有洗漱.
Mike: How else is he going to hear me?Hey dad, if you want me to go to the gym with you,I'm already.I didn't shower and everything.
开萝尔:他在睡觉,迈克.
Carol: He's in bed Mike.
迈克:他还在睡觉?九点半了.
Mike: What's he doing asleep?Its nine thirty.
开萝尔:我可没说他在睡觉.
Carol: I didn't say he was sleeping.
迈克:哦!又是周末.
Mike: Oh!One of those Saturdays.
本:什么周末?
Ben: One of what Saturdays?
迈克:你知道……
Mike: You know...
开萝尔:迈克,注意点.
Carol: Mike, do you mind.
克莉丝:好象我没有听见过粗话!
Chrissy: Like I haven't heard worse around here!
本:你们谈些什么呢?
Ben: What are you guys talking about?
迈克:嗨,本,回去看你的卡通吧.
Mike: Hey Ben, go back to your cartoons.
本:不是我的卡通.如果是我,一定支持金黄色组.现在爸和妈在楼上干嘛?
Ben: They're not my cartoons.If it was up to me I'd be up to hee in the blonde division.Now what are mum and dad doing upstairs
迈克:你真的不知道?过来,本.
Mike: You seriously don't know?Come on Ben.
开萝尔:克莉丝.
Carol: Chrissy.
迈克:我们见过.
Mike: We've met.
开萝尔:不,我们在说你.
Carol: No, what we are talking about.
迈克:听着,本,
Mike: Look Ben, what do little horn balls your age think of every waking
像你这个岁数的小混球醒着的时候,在想些什么?
hour of their lives?
克莉丝:吃的.
Chrissy: food.
本:嘿!她枪了我的答案.
Ben: Hey, she took my answer.
开萝尔:我看捂上克莉丝的耳朵比较安全.
Carol: I think it's safe to let go of Chrissy's ears.
本:除了吃的,还会想什么?
Ben: Its not food, what else ids there?
迈克:你会吐的?
Mike: It makes you want to puke hu?
本:太笨了.
Ben: So stupid.
克莉丝:他也明白了.
Chrissy: So he knows too.
迈克:你知道的,爸爸.这就是生活的全部. 出出汗,爸爸.
Mike: You know dad.This is what life is all about.Sweating with your father.
杰森:花了一年才把你弄来.
Jason: It took me a year to get you here.
迈克:你等等.我保证下次不会超过一年再来.
Mike: You wait.It sure won't be a year until I come back.
杰森:你需要什么,迈克?
Jason: What are you after Mike?
迈克:行了.你真以为我说这些,
Mike: Come on.You honestly think I'm saying all this just to hit you up
是为了向你讨几块钱.
for a few dollars?
杰森:几个?
Jason: How few?
迈克:两百.埃迪和我要去海边度假村.
Mike: Two hundred.Eddie and I want to go in on a beach house.
杰森:在哪?
Jason: Where?
迈克:这么,这得看你给我多少钱.
Mike: Well, it kind of depends on how this goes.
杰森:你连沙滩都别想靠近,迈克.
Jason: You are nowhere near the sand Mike.
迈克:哦,哦!
Mike: Wow!Wow!
女士:嗨,杰森.瞧瞧你!
Lady: Hey Jase.Look at you!
杰森:我更愿瞧瞧你,格雷琴.
Jason: I'd rather look at you Gretchen.
格雷琴:你真的进步了.
Gretchen: You are really coming along.
杰森:谢谢.谢谢.
Jason: Thank you.Thank you.
格雷琴:你的胸肌很发达.
Gretchen: Your chest looks strong.
杰森:是呀,想看它跳舞吗?
Jason: Yeah, want to see it dance.
格雷琴:你真的变结实了.
Gretchen: You are really firming up.
杰森:那里有人叫我.
Jason: Well hello there.
格雷琴:待会见 .
Gretchen: I'll see you later.
杰森:再见!
Jason: See you.
迈克:不错呀,爸爸.
Mike: Alright dad.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What.
杰森:那是个女人!
Mike: That was a woman.
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
迈克:而且她真的对你感兴趣.
Mike: And she was actually coming on to you.
杰森:偶然碰见而已.
Jason: It happens occasionally.
迈克:而且你对她也有意思.
Mike: And you were coming on to her.
杰森:得啦.你在开玩笑.我没有发现她有魅力.
Jason: Come on.Are you kidding.I barely noticed she was attractive.
迈克:哦,行了,
Mike: Oh come on dad.You do exactly what I do with women.
爸爸.你对待女人和我一样.只是不如我.
Only not so well.
杰森:我不知道你在说些什么,迈克.
Jason: I don't know what you are talking about Mike.
我只不过对她客气..
I was just being nice to her
迈克:客气?爸爸,你是在调情.你是已婚男人.
Mike: Nice!Dad you were flirting.And you're a married man.
杰森:这样的话,结了婚,你就不能和女人说话了.
Jason: Since when did being married mean that you can't talk to a woman
迈克:爸爸,我不说这个了.我只想说两百美元,妈就永远不需要回答这问题了.
Mike: Dad, I'm not saying that.All I'm saying is that for just two hundred dollars, mum may never need to answer that question.
杰森:迈克,迈克,
Jason: Mike, Mike.You have no idea what a worthwhile relationship is all
迈克.你根本对什么是有价值的关系概念都没有.
about.
迈克:一百七十五?
Mike: One seventy-five?
杰森:就凭你的消息,你妈妈不仅不会介意我和姑娘一起聊天,而且在我看来,这是我的职业内在本能,我猜你妈妈一定会这有趣.
Jason: For your information, not only would your mother not mind if a young lady
and I shot the breeze, but it is my opinion, and this is my professional
gut instinct, my guess is that your mother would think it's kind of cute
迈克:有趣!
Mike: Cute!
杰森:是,有趣,
Jason: Yeah cute.Cos what happens you see, is that when your mother sees me,
因为你所看到的发生的事情,就是当你妈妈能理解我的,你知道…..
you know...
迈克:你就吹吧.
Mike: Shooting the breeze.
杰森:吹牛,和其他女人,这会提醒她,我是属于她,她有一宝.
Jason: Shooting the breeze, with another woman, it reminds her that I belong to her
and she has something of value
迈克:一百一十五,就当什么都没发生.
Mike: One fifteen this never happened.
麦琪:本.
Maggie: Ben.
本:这.
Ben: Yes.
麦琪:本,你应该和克莉丝玩玩了.
Maggie: Ben, you are supposed to be entertaining Chrissy.
本:我在和她玩.
Ben: I am.
克莉丝:本,商业广告结束了.你要错过金黄色的叠罗汉了.
Chrissy: Ben, the commercial's over.You are missing a blonde pyramid.
本:没关系,我在录.
Ben: Its ok, I'm taping it.
麦琪:出什么事了?
Maggie: Is anything wrong?
本:没有.
Ben: No.
麦琪:你想谈点什么事情吗?
Maggie: Did you want to talk about something?
本:你有什么事情想跟我谈的吗?
Ben: Did you want to talk to me about something?
麦琪:本,你遇上什么事情了?你看上去比平时失落和困惑.
Maggie: Ben do you have a problem?You look more lost and confused than usual.
本:我只是惊讶.
Ben: Let's just say I'm stunned.
麦琪:惊讶什么?
Maggie: About what?
本:对你无可奉告.我需要自己的空间.
Ben: Nothing I can talk to you about.I need my space.
麦琪:好吧.无论什么时候你想和我谈谈你所担心的事情,
Maggie: Well ok.Well whenever you want to talk about whatever's on your mind,
我都可以.
I'm available.
本:那是我所听到的.
Ben: That's what I hear.
麦琪:本,本.过来.你知道,
Maggie: Ben, Ben.Come here.You know honey, you can ask me anything.
亲爱的,你可以问我任何方面.我也有过你的年龄.也曾是个烦恼的孩子,皮肤不好.
I was once your age.I was once a confused kid with bad skin too.
本:我皮肤怎么了?
Ben: What's wrong with my skin?
麦琪:哦,没什么,小甜心?我是说我也是人.
Maggie: oh nothing sweetheart.I just meant that I'm human.
本:人.她也是人!从什么时候开始?她是人.
Ben: Human.She's human!Since when?She's human.So is dad.They have needs.
爸也是.他们有需求.他们某时也把他们的内裤从一条腿上脱下.父母也是人.
They take their pants off one leg at a time.Parents are people!
开萝尔:本,你有多大胆让妹妹一个人在看金黄色的叠罗汉.
Carol: Ben, how dare you have our little sister watch a blonde pyramid.
哦!
Oh and now you hit me on the head with a banana.
现在又用香蕉打我的头.你为什么这么做?
How did you do that?
麦琪:哦!克莉丝!
Maggie: Oh Chrissy!
克莉丝:不是我干的.
Chrissy: I didn't do it.
麦琪:本,我以为你应该照看你的妹妹.
Maggie: Ben, I thought you were supposed to be watching your sister.
本:我照看着呢.
Ben: I am.
迈克:爸爸,我想知道你为什么你对送毛巾的小伙子,
Mike: Dad, I just want to know why you weren't as nice to the towel guy
不如对送果汁的小姐那么好呢?
as you were to the juice bunny.
杰森:好,好,好吧.我承认.也许我对那送果汁姑娘,是要比对那送毛巾小子好一点.我不认为你妈不会在意我对那些对我好的人礼貌些.说完了.
Jason: Ok, ok.Alright.I admit.Maybe I was a little nicer to the juice
girl than I was to the towel guy.I don't think your mother would mind
that I'm a little nice to people who are a little nice to me.Nough
said
迈克:你以为妈妈傻到相信你的话.
Mike: Like mum's dumb enough to buy that.
麦琪:妈妈傻到相信什么?
Maggie: Like mums dumb enough to buy what?
克莉丝:嗨,爸爸.
Chrissy: Hi daddy.
杰森:嗨,宝贝.妆是不是化的太浓了点?
Jason: Hi sweetheart.Isn't that a bit too much make up?
麦琪:别转变话题.妈妈傻到相信什么?
Maggie: Don't change the subject.Mum's not dumb enough to buy what.
杰森:真高兴你在这,麦琪.
Jason: I'm glad you're here Maggie.
你得帮我向这孩子证明一些事情.
I need you to help me demonstrate something to the boy.
麦琪:可以.
Maggie: Ok.
杰森:看起来迈克在这方面,有错误的认识,认为你,一个女人一定火冒三丈,如果我,一个男人,和另外的女人说话.                                               迈克:说呀!哈哈.
Jason: It seems that Mike here, has the mistaken impression that you, as a woman
would be upset if I, as a man, were to speak to another woman.Mike
Speak!Ha ha
麦琪:什么呀?
Maggie: Pardon me?
杰森:没什么,亲爱的.过来.我们只是谈话.
Jason: Nothing honey.Come on.All we did was talk.
麦琪:谁?
Maggie: Who?
迈克:很显然,她喜欢边说边动手动脚.
Mike: Well apparently she likes to talk with her hands.
麦琪:谁?
Maggie: Who?
杰森:行了.她不过拍了拍我的肚子,摸了摸我的胸肌.
Jason: Come on.She merely patted my stomach and tapped my chest.
迈克:还捏了捏你的屁股.
Mike: And grabbed your butt.
麦琪:你们在说谁?
Maggie: Who are you talking about?
迈克和杰森:格雷琴.
Mike and Jason: Gretchen.
麦琪:哦,格雷琴.
Maggie: Oh Gretchen.Who in the hell is Gretchen,
到底谁是格雷琴,还有她在那里捏你的?
and where did she grab you again?
杰森:在健身房.迈克有错误的认识,
Jason: In the gym.
认为你,一个女人一定火冒三丈,
Mike has the mistaken impression that you as a woman would be upset if me,
如果我,一个男人……
as a man...
麦琪:杰森,告诉我你想说的?
Maggie: Jason, just tell me what you are trying to say?
迈克:是呀,爸爸.我也想听听你怎么解释那个小宝贝.
Mike: Yeah dad.I'd kind of like to hear how you explain this babe too.
杰森:别在这乱说什么了.小宝贝不会捏我,迈克.一个女人.
Jason: Let's not be chauvinistic here.A babe did not grab me Mike.A woman.
麦琪:说什么?
Maggie: What?
迈克:想想,我们本来可以避免这丑陋是的.
Mike: And to think we could have avoided all this ugliness.
杰森:不公平.我所做的我不过是对她稍微好一点罢了.
Jason: It's not fair.Now all I did was to be nice to her.
麦琪:好到什么地步?
Maggie: How nice?
杰森:我这么说吧.基本上和对送毛巾小子的态度基本一样.
Jason: Let me put it this way.I was basically the same to the towel guy.
迈克:算了吧,爸爸.那个送毛巾小子可没捏你的屁股.
Mike: Come on dad.The towel guy didn't pat you on the behind.
杰森:他可以捏.没人阻止他.
Jason: He could have.Nobody was stopping him.
麦琪:好,好,等一等.
Maggie: now, now wait a minute.
杰森:很简单.我一个男人,对一个女人……
Jason: It's very simple.I was just as a man, to a woman...
麦琪:不是你说,杰森,迈克?
Maggie: Not you Jason.Mike?
迈克:妈妈,小妞挑逗爸爸.
Mike: Mum, this babe goosed dad.
杰森:哦!太夸张了.
Jason: Oh, that's such an exaggeration.It was so innocent.
我是清白的.我们只不过在一起讨论了一下我的身体而已.
And it all developed out of a conversation about my body.
麦琪:哈哈哈.哦,我肯定你爸爸说"你好啊".
Maggie: Ha ha ha.And I bet your dad went "well hello there".
杰森:你太了解我了,麦琪.
Jason: You know me too well Maggie.
麦琪:是呀,这当然了,亲爱的.
Maggie: Yes I sure do honey.
迈克:你真的不在乎,是吗?
Mike: You really don't mind, do you?
杰森:希望有一天你也有像你妈和我这么成熟的关系.
Jason: And we hope that one day you will have a mature relationship like
your mum and me do.
迈克:算了,我才不呢.
Mike: Well I don't.I think this is kind of sick.
我是觉得有点不对劲.妈妈,如果我有个丈夫,
Mum, if I had a husband and he was flirting around with other women,
他在外面和其他女人调情,我一定十分恼火的.
I would be pretty upset.
杰森:我们也会.
Jason: So would we.
迈克:妈妈,你会觉得这有趣吗?
Mike: Mum, how can you think this is cute?
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: Pardon me?
迈克:是这样,爸觉得你会认为,
Mike: Yes, dad thinks that you think it's cute when he flirts with other
他与别人调情是件很有趣的事情,因为这样使你觉得自己是个幸运的玩偶.
women because it makes you feel like a lucky doll.
怎么样,爸爸,
How dad, why don't you give mum a real hoot and take this babe out for
你为什么不给妈一个真正的搅拌,带小宝贝去兜风呢?
a spin?
杰森:孩子,他要学的还多着呢,呵?
Jason: Boy, he's got a lot to learn, hu?
杰森:麦琪,晚餐还有十分钟.
Jason: Maggie, dinner reservation's in ten minutes.
开萝尔,要让克莉丝八点上床睡觉.
Carol, make sure Chrissy's in bed by eight.
克莉丝:九点.
Chrissy: Nine.
杰森:八点十五.
Jason: Eight fifteen.
克莉丝:八点四十五.
Chrissy: Eight forty five.
杰森:八点三十.
Jason: Eight thirty.
克莉丝:成交.
Chrissy: Done.
杰森:我最熟悉这一套了.
Jason: I'm getting too old for this.
迈克:嗨,爸爸,还是你交汽车保险吗?
Mike: Hey dad, am I still covered by your auto insurance?
杰森:是啊.
Jason: Yeah.
迈克:好.
Mike: Good.
杰森:什么?好!为什么?
Jason: What?Good!Why?
迈克:不,不.
Mike: No, no.I didn't get in an accident.
我没出交通事故.
It's just that well,
既然是那样,
since I am now financially unable to afford a beach house,
因为我没钱支付海边小屋,这夏天我就多开开车了.
I'm going to be doing a lot of driving this summer.
杰森:当我没问.我们只有八分钟了,麦琪.
Jason: Sorry I asked.Reservations in eight minutes Maggie.
迈克:呵,你们都打扮好了.
Mike: So, you are all dressed up.
杰森:是啊.今天带你妈出去共进晚餐.
Jason: Yes.I'm taking your mother out for a little dinner this evening.
迈克:穿上献殷勤的衣服.
Mike: In your groveling suit.
杰森:我没有献殷勤.这不是献殷情.
Jason: I'm not groveling.This isn't groveling.
这是精心安排,一个自然的夜晚.
No I just carefully planned a spontaneous evening.
迈克:哎,妈对你调情一定很恼火,是吗?
Mike: well mum must be pretty upset about your flirting, hu?
杰森:她没恼火,我也没调情.
Jason: No she isn't and I didn't.You know, women can be strange.
你知道,女人会很奇怪.
Who knows what is really the matter.
谁知道是什么问题呢.也许是今早一件衣服不合身了.也许觉得自己老了.
Maybe one of her dresses didn't fit this morning.Maybe it's the age thing.
也许觉得好时光过去了.也许……
Maybe she feels that her best years are behind her.Maybe...
麦琪:也许是我的婚姻的缘故.
Maggie: Maybe it's my marriage.
杰森:也许.迈克,永远不要再和我说话.
Jason: Maybe.Mike, don't ever talk to me again.
迈克:永远?
Mike: Ever?
杰森:永远.永远.
Jason: Ever.Ever
服务生:选择酒是不错.
Waiter: An excellent choice of wine.
杰森:谢谢,马库斯.
Jason: Thank you Marcus.
服务生:请享用.难道花钱不开心吗?
Waiter: Enjoy.Isn't it fun to spend money?
杰森:我今晚甚至还想要点个汤.
Jason: I may even order soup tonight.
不错,虽然你和我能单独出来,
Good idea though, you and I being out alone, don't you think?
你不认为吗?
Just a spare of the moment kind of thing.
有点心血来潮,这是一个不是特殊日子的特殊场合.
A special occasion with no special occasion.
我只是想找个机会告诉我对你真的感觉.
I just wanted a chance to tell you how I truly feel about you.
麦琪:我很高兴.
Maggie: I'm happy.
杰森:另外,你很漂亮.我说过吗?
Jason: And you are beautiful.Did I mention that?
麦琪:大概十六遍了.
Maggie: About sixteen times.
杰森:应该第十七遍,你很漂亮.
Jason: Well for the seventeenth, you are beautiful.
麦琪:再说一遍,谢谢,谢谢.
Maggie: Well thank you again, again.
杰森:好吧,看看该先吃点什么呢?
Jason: So, what shall we start off with here?
麦琪:什么都不错.哦,
Maggie: Well everything looks so good.
我要份野鸳鸯.
Oh, I think I'll have the goose liver pate.
杰森:很好,好,好.请你说清楚,
Jason: Fine, ok, ok.Let's just deal with.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
麦琪:鸳鸯,麦琪.你说野鸳鸯.
Jason: Goose Maggie.You said goose.I know what you are aiming at here Maggie.
你在这指的是什么,我知道.讲吧.
Come on.
麦琪:杰森,你在说什么啊?
Maggie: Jason, what in the world are you talking about?
杰森:我在说什么,麦琪?红烧鸳鸯.
Jason: What am I talking about Maggie?Pate, the goose.
麦琪:哦,我瞧瞧,八宝鸡胸脯.
Maggie: Oh lets see, stuffed chicken breast.No.
不,还有黄油龙虾,这是个选择.
Oh see lobster with drawn butter, that a possibility.
杰森:真平静.
Jason: Very smooth.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:麦琪,是吧.
Jason: Maggie, come on.
自从迈克说了体育馆里的话,你老是含沙射影.
You've been on my back ever since Mike said about the gym.
麦琪:杰森,我什么都没说.
Maggie: Jason, I haven't said a word.
杰森:你说的每个词都没我知道的其他女人响亮.
Jason: Well you don't say a word louder than any woman I know.
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
杰森:麦琪,你难道不是有目的去选择单词?什么呀.
Jason: Maggie, you just didn't use those words on purpose?Come on.
野鸳鸯,胸脯,黄油龙虾.
Goose, breast, drawn butter.
麦琪:河豚.
Maggie: Drawn butter?
杰森:就是.拉黄油.
Jason: That's right.Drawn butter.
如果你想说什么就直说,亲爱的.
If you've got something to say just say it honey.
麦琪:亲爱的,没什么.我理解.我没有发火.
Maggie: Honey, it's ok.I understand.I am not upset.
杰森:你没有?
Jason: You're not?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.
杰森:好吧.为我俩.
Jason: Ok.To us.
麦琪:就别和我调情了.
Maggie: Just don't do your flirting around me.
杰森:麦琪,我没有调情.
Jason: Maggie, I wasn't flirting.
麦琪:那你说是什么?
Maggie: Then what would you call it?
杰森:我不知道.但是我没调情.
Jason: I don't know.But I didn't flirt.
麦琪:好吧,亲爱的.
Maggie: Ok honey, how would you like it if I didn't flirt,
如果我不调情,你怎么想,像你不调情?
like you didn't flirt?
杰森:我一点不介意.
Jason: I wouldn't mind at all.
麦琪:哦,你不会介意,如果我对服务生说"好臀"?
Maggie: oh you wouldn't mind if I said to the waiter "nice buns"?
服务生:为什么?谢谢你.
Waiter: Why thank you.
麦琪:不用谢.
Maggie: You're welcome.
杰森:你认为我到处向女人说这种话,麦琪?
Jason: Do you think I'm walking around saying that kind of thing to women
因为我没说.
Maggie?Cos I'm not.
麦琪:这样,杰森,是她们对你说.
Maggie: Well Jason, they are saying it to you.
杰森:你认为我这样的美臀,能不引人注目吗?
Jason: Do you think it's easy walking around with a rear end like this?
幽默一下,就轻松愉快了.
From this jocularity a good time will grow.
麦琪:好,好,我们无法进行严肃的话题,你的中年综合症.
Maggie: Fine, fine, we wont have a serious conversation about you middle aged insecurity
杰森:我还没到中年.
Jason: I'm not middle aged.
麦琪:哦,你打算活到八十六岁?
Maggie: Oh, you plan to live to be eighty-six?
杰森:差不多了.得了,麦琪,
Jason: Not happily.Come on Maggie, I know men who flirt.
我知道男人调情.我见过男人调情.甚至有一两个人向我调情.
I've seen men who flirt.I've even had a fellow or two flirt with me, ok.
好,但是我告诉你,我所做的不是调情.
And I'm telling you that what I do isn't flirting.
麦琪:很好.如果你可以忍受.
Maggie: Fine.If you can live with that.
杰森:如果我和别人眉目传情,我暗示我希望关系暧昧,
Jason: If I make eye contact with a woman and I imply that maybe I would
然后她,也许有些亲昵行为,
like to be intimate, and then she, there's some intimacy that, uh, um,
啊哈,一些……我说到哪了?
some, ...Well where was I?
麦琪:哦!杰森.
Maggie: Oh Jason.
杰森:我没有调情,只能说是注意,
Jason: I was not flirting.See that was just noticing Maggie.I'm a doctor.
麦琪.我是个医生.她非常健康.
She was very healthy.
麦琪:杰森,难道你不应该向我道歉吗?
Maggie: Jason, for me cant you just apologize?
杰森:好了,对不起.
Jason: Ok, I'm sorry.I am sorry.
对不起.等我想明白了,我知道错在哪,
And as soon as I figure out what I did wrong I'll never do it again.
保证绝不这样了.现在开吃吧.
Now let's eat.
杰森:跳舞去.
Jason: Lets dance.
本:开萝尔,如果爸妈是普通人,会改变一切.
Ben: Well Carol, if mum and dad are just people, that change everything.
开萝尔:你说的有道理,本.
Carol: There's a thought there Ben.
本:开萝尔,你根本没在听我说话.
Ben: Carol, you are not listening to me.
开萝尔:你说的有道理,本.
Carol: There's a thought there Ben.
本:开萝尔!
Ben: Carol!
开萝尔:好吧.他们当然是人.听着,
Carol: Ok.Of course they're people Ben.
对你这个斜前额来说,这也许是一个重大的发现,
Look, these may be giant discoveries for someone with a sloped forehead,
但我对他们不感兴趣.六岁时,我就有这些想法了.
but they don't interest me.I had those thoughts when I was six.
本:你是说,爸爸妈妈一直是人,
Ben: You mean you knew that mum and dad were human being all along and
而从来没有告诉我.
you never told me?
开萝尔:得了,你会信我吗?
Carol: Well would you have believed me?
本:不!这样,爸和我一样?
Ben: No.So dad's just like me?
开萝尔:很不幸.
Carol: Unfortunately.
本:你也看了他床下的杂志了?
Ben: You've actually seen the magazines under his bed?
开萝尔:我去叫醒克莉丝,跳支幸福的舞来庆祝一下我们是女孩.
Carol: I'm going to wake Chrissy up so we can do a happy dance that
we are girls
麦琪:晚安!本.
Maggie: Goodnight Ben.
杰森:你妈和我有点累,
Jason: Mum and I are a little tired,
我们要上楼睡觉了.
so we are going to go up to bed.
本:好的,爸爸.
Ben: Alright dad!
杰森:好了,你今晚一定出尽风头了.
Jason: Well, you certainly made a spectacle of yourself tonight.
麦琪:哦,你介意我和英俊男士跳兰巴达?
Maggie: Oh, you minded me doing the Lambada with a handsome man?
杰森:麦琪,那根本就没舞池.
Jason: Maggie, there was no dance floor.
要是更挑剔的话,那也没音乐.
And just to be picky about it, there was no music.
麦琪:没有吗?
Maggie: There wasn't?
杰森:啊哈!我告诉你,
Jason: Uh hu.And for your information, the Lambada is a forbidden dance.
兰巴达是禁舞.这就是我得到的报答,
These are the thanks I get Maggie?
麦琪?结婚二十二年来,
I have been true to you for every second of the twenty-two years we've
我每时每刻对你都是真心的,麦琪.
been married Maggie.And I can say this to you,
而且我可以这么对你说,我从来没有坏的想法,
I've never had a serious thought, I can say this,
我可以说,我从没有要欺骗你的坏想法.
I have never had a serious thought about cheating on you.
麦琪:我们谈谈你的轻佻的想法.
Maggie: Well then let's deal with your frivolous thoughts.
杰森:我对你失望了,麦琪.
Jason: I'm disappointed in you Maggie.
麦琪:哦.你对我失望.
Maggie: Oh.You're disappointed in me.
杰森:对,这么多年来,
Jason: Yeah, after all these years of you saying you don't mind if I exchange
你一直在对我说,不介意我和女人开玩笑.现在我发现你一直在说谎.
pleasantries with women.Now I found out you were lying.
对我还有什么隐瞒的,麦琪?
What else have you held from me Maggie?
麦琪:杰森,
Maggie: Jason, if it wouldn't be too much trouble,
如果没有什么困难的话,我们先来谈谈你的中年危机,
could we please deal first with your midlife crisis,
然后再谈谈你的风流艳史.
before we deal with your insanity?
杰森:哦,可以.
Jason: Oh yeah.Just as long as we keep enough time open to deal with your
可也得留下足够的时间来谈谈你在那家高档饭店里的可恶行为.
outrageous behavior at that expensive restaurant.
麦琪:那可没有捏屁股,除非舞蹈的确需要这样做.
Maggie: There were no bottoms grabbed, except when the dance called for it.
杰森:那么,我也没有对她做什么.
Jason: Well I didn't do anything to her.
麦琪:哦,对.
Maggie: Oh right.
杰森:哦,麦琪,行了.瞧瞧当前潜在的事实.
Jason: Oh Maggie, come on.Look at the subconscious facts here.
我跟一个女人说话,是因为她的高度,头发,
I talked to a woman your height, your hair color, your eye color,
眼睛,颜色都像你,不过她稍微带点琥珀色.这又能向你说明什么呢?
except little flecks of amber in hers.But what does that tell you?
麦琪:这就说明你跟她的凑的太近.
Maggie: It tells me that you were too stinking close to her.
杰森:不,麦琪,这说明,
Jason: No Maggie.What it says is that symbolically I am really flirting
下意识里我是在在向你调情.你不该发火,你应该感到荣幸.
with you.Not only should you not be mad, you should be honored.
麦琪:我应该去听戏.
Maggie: I should have listened to Oprah.
你不能指望婚姻,
You cant count on a marriage even when it has lasted for twenty two years
即使这婚姻已经维持二十二年四个月.
and four months.
杰森:戏里面不会上演这些.
Jason: Oprah didn't do a show on that.
麦琪:我刚才的意思是说,
Maggie: Her point being that a woman shouldn't trust her marriage when
女人不应该相信建立在上了年纪的男人的不稳定心理因素上的婚姻.
it's built on the fragile psyche of the aging male.
杰森:哦,是的,那是菲尔 多洛修说的?
Jason: Oh yeah, well what does Phil Donohue say?
麦琪:哦,杰森,我怎么了?
Maggie: Oh Jason, what's wrong with me?
杰森:什么事情让你去认为事情不妙呢,麦琪?
Jason: What makes you think anything's wrong with you Maggie?
麦琪:我不再让你兴奋了?
Maggie: Don't I excite you anymore?
杰森:不再了.我们也不小了.
Jason: Not any more.Not any less either.
喔,喔,他在哪想到这些的?
Ho ho, where does he come up with these?
麦琪:承认吧,杰森,
Maggie: Admit it Jason,
你觉得一个二十岁,
you find a twenty-year-old woman with a fully conditioned body and beautiful
体格健美,有漂亮头发和眼睛的姑娘很有吸引力?
hair and eyes attractive?
杰森:麦琪,小甜心.有了你,
Jason: Maggie sweetheart.What do I need with a beautiful woman when I've
我还要漂亮女人干什么?麦琪,我意思是说,你很漂亮,
got you?Maggie, I mean, you were so beautiful, you're not young.
你不再年轻.你也不老,我不是那个意思.
You're not old, I didn't mean that.
麦琪:哦,省省吧,
Maggie: Oh save it Jason.
杰森.
Don't you see what happened today was simply a reflex ion of your
难道你不明白,今天发生的事情不是你下意识需要的简单反应吗?
subconscious need?
杰森:不,小甜心.
Jason: No sweetheart.I don't.I'll tell you what I do see.
我没有.我告诉你我看到了什么?我看到一个进入更年期的女人无理取闹.
I see a woman going through middle aged crisis for no reason what so ever.
麦琪:你真认为我无理取闹?
Maggie: You really don't think I have a reason?
杰森:行了,亲爱的.
Jason: Come on honey.You're gorgeous.You're intelligent.
你很美丽.你又很聪明.今天你比我第一次见到的时候更好.
You're better today than the day i met you.
麦琪:哦!杰森.
Maggie: Oh Jason.
杰森:那我们为什么吵架?
Jason:So Why are we arguing?
麦琪:我不记得了.
Maggie: I don't remember.
杰森:很好.
Jason: Good.
麦琪:我记起来了.亲爱的,
Maggie: Yes I do.Honey it's not your flirting.It's your attitude.
不是因为你去调情.而是由于你的态度.你一直坚持说你自己什么都没有做错.
It's your unrelenting sureness that you have done nothing wrong.
杰森:你确定吗?你对此确定吗?
Jason: Are you sure?Are you sure about that?Because what I thought....
因为我想……我想什么没关系.
it doesn't matter what I thought.
麦琪:杰森,你真的还不明白吗,明白了吗?
Maggie: Jason, you just don't get it, do you?
杰森:麦琪,告诉我你需要什么?
Jason: Maggie, tell me what you want?
麦琪:我要你感到愧疚.
Maggie: I want you to have some guilt.
杰森:没问题.
Jason: Done.
麦琪:还有自觉.
Maggie: And some awareness too.
杰森:你明白了,麦琪.
Jason: You got it Maggie.
麦琪:杰森,有时候你真的很愚蠢.
Maggie: Jason, sometimes you are so thick.
我是说,不管你有没有调情,
I mean whether you flirted or not, right or wrong,
对还是错,想一想,
think for a second if it might appear to me that you might have flirted.
如果我可能意识到你已经调情了.那样我会有什么感受?
Then how would I feel?
杰森:这么说,如果你认为没有事情是有事情,
Jason: So if you thought that nothing was something, even,
甚至,甚至没有事情是没有事情,然后,
even if nothing was nothing, then,
你认为没有事情是有事情的话,就是我伤害了你.麦琪,
the fact that you think that nothing was something means that I hurt you.
我是蠢蛋.我感到难受.
Maggie, I'm a slope headed jerk.I feel terrible.
麦琪:好极了.
Maggie: Great.
杰森:你认为我难受的好?
Jason: You think it's great I feel terrible?
麦琪:是呀,我就这么认为的.
Maggie: Yes I do.
杰森:我怎么会这么反映迟钝?我是烂人.请原谅我.
Jason: How could I be so insensitive?I am the worse person.Please forgive me.
麦琪:亲爱的,没关系.
Maggie: Honey it's ok.
杰森:这怎么没关系?
Jason: How can it be ok?
麦琪:因为我才发现,
Maggie: Because I just found out that your midlife crisis is worse than
你的中年危机问题要比我的严重.
my midlife crisis.
杰森:你知道在世界上什么地方现在还是周六的早晨?
Jason: You know somewhere in the world it is still Saturday morning.
格雷琴:你父母不会介意我们拿走所有的食物?
Gretchen:: Your parents don't mind us taking all this food?
迈克:哦,不是.只要不动他们的纤维食品.
Mike: Oh no.Just as long as I don't touch their fiber.
麦琪:杰森,我去拿纤维食品.
Maggie: Jason, I'll get the fiber.
迈克:哎,妈妈,格雷琴.
Mike: Ah mum, meet Gretchen.
格雷琴:你好.
Gretchen: Hi.
麦琪:我感觉我好像见过你,天哪,是琥珀色.
Maggie: I feel like I already have.Damn, they are amber.
杰森:哦,我饿死了.哦,你好.
Jason: Oh, I'm starved.Oh hi.
格雷琴:你好.
Gretchen: Hi.
杰森:出去.
Jason: get out.
迈克:哦,待会见.
Mike: Oh,ok, we'll see you later.
格雷琴:很高兴见到你
Gretchen: Nice to meet you.
麦琪:西维尔太太.
Maggie: Mrs.Seaver.
格雷琴:真有趣.在你打电话约我时,我还不知道你爸爸已经结婚了呢?
Gretchen: That's funny.Before you called me up for a date,
杰森:她该问一下.00:22:41,600
I didn't have a clue your dad was married. Jason: She could have asked.